And so...
所以
the center at JIF will be Kana Arima!
日本偶像节的C位将是有马加奈!
Woot! Applause!
耶 鼓掌
Give us a comment about how you feel being chosen as the center!
跟我们说说当选C位的感觉
Let's see.
我想想
First, turn that camera off.
首先 关掉摄像机
I told you, right?
我告诉过你们的吧?
That I didn't want to be the center numerous times.
我说过很多次了 我不想当C位
Is this what I think it is?
是我想的这样吗?
You think an easy pushover like me
你们以为我耳根子很软
wouldn't be able to refuse later if you guys made it a fact on camera?
如果你们在镜头前做实这事 我就不会拒绝了吗?
Crap, she knows!
糟了 她知道
Uh, well!
好吧
Ruby and I talked about it when we went to karaoke together.
我跟露比一起去唱卡拉OK的时候 聊到了这事
But we came to the conclusion that neither of us would make a good center.
我们得出的结论是 我们俩谁也当不好C位
And that's when we saw the music video for your song...
然后我们看到了你的音乐视频...
So you guys saw it.
所以你们看到了
They mistakenly thought I could sing since "Green Pepper Exercise" sold pretty well,
因为《青椒运动》销量很好 他们就误以为我会唱歌
and everyone got burned for it.
结果大家都因此受到了伤害
Forget you saw it. That's a symbol of the days when I was lost.
就当你们没看过吧 那是一段迷失自我的日子
The dark ages of when I lost my way in this field.
我在这个圈子里迷失方向的黑暗时代
You don't need to say it like that.
你不需要那样说
Well, I almost peed my pants seeing how little it sold.
看到销量那么少 我差点尿裤子
Everyone who was affiliated wants to put it behind them.
参与制作的人都想忘记那件事
To be honest, I thought "Green Pepper Exercise" was off-key.
老实说 我觉得《青椒运动》跑调了
But your second song was really good.
但是你第二首歌真的很好听
And your third song was even better.
第三首歌更好听
You must've practiced a lot, huh?
你肯定经过了大量的练习吧?
You worked really hard trying to live up to everyone's expectations.
为了不辜负大家的期望 你真的非常努力
Someone as responsible as you should be the center of B Komachi...
像前辈这样负责任的人 才应该当B小町的C位
Shut up!
吵死了!
You think I'll give in if you just keep buttering me up, don't you?!
你们以为一直恭维我 我就会屈服吗?
Do you think I'm stupid?!
你们以为我傻吗?
I seriously can't do this.
我真的做不到
No matter how many times you ask, I won't become the center!
无论你们问多少次 我都不想当C位
Sorry we acted without talking to you.
对不起 我们没跟你说就行动了
We won't ask anymore.
我们不会再这样做了
But at least listen to our singing.
但至少听听我们的歌声吧
Hey, isn't this pretty good?!
这不是很好吗?
I knew Arima would be perfect as the center!
我就知道有马是完美的C位
At this rate, we'll do great at the JIF!
照这个速度 我们可以在日本偶像节上大放异彩了
Ugh, jeez! Why am I always like this?!
天啊 我为什么总是这样?
Well, I never thought that we could turn the tables from that hellish situation.
真没想到我们能扭转 前面那番地狱般的氛围
I had a feeling it would turn out this way from the start.
我一开始就预感到会变成这样
Shut up, Quirky and Off-key!
闭嘴 又怪又跑调
I never thought that idol candidates could be this terrible at singing.
我从没想过 偶像候选人唱歌会这么难听
Based on your singing,
根据你的歌声
I can see the comfortable lives you led by relying on just your looks.
我能看出 你的确是靠脸吃饭的
Brutal.
真残忍啊
It's true that I should be the one to do it.
的确该由我来当这个C位
But I honestly don't want to do it.
但老实说 我不想当
Seriously, what would you guys do without me?!
说真的 没有我你们可怎么办?
Just make sure to work hard to make me stand out!
好好努力 让我脱颖而出
Okay!
好的
Well, I'm glad it worked out!
我好高兴啊 成功了
Why does my mouth always say the opposite of what I'm thinking?
为什么我嘴上说的 总跟我心里想的相反?
Looks like it's settled then.
看起来已经解决了
CEO!
总裁
There's barely any days left until the concert.
离现场演出没有几天了
And this is where you really need to push yourselves.
这正是你们需要努力的地方
I've grabbed someone to support you, so make good use of him.
我找人来帮你们了 好好利用
Someone to support us?
有人来帮我们?
Is that perhaps Aqu--
那有没有可能是阿...
- Hey. - Wait, it's you?!
-喂 -等等 是你?
Oh, Pieyon, long time no see!
啾啾仔 好久不见
What? The real thing?!
什么?是本尊?
You're our top seller!
你是我们最赚钱的艺人
I'm begging you, please work normally!
求求你 去做你自己的日常工作!
Well, Mr. Pieyon used to be a pro dancer before!
啾啾仔先生以前当过职业舞者
He said in his videos that he used to choreograph for idols too.
他在视频里说 他以前也给偶像编舞
Really?
真的吗?
How do we look from a pro's point of view?
从专业人士的角度来看 我们怎么样?
I think we're somewhat in shape now.
我认为我们现在有点状态
Hmm, well, there's a ton of girls around your level who perform on stage.
登台表演的女孩中 跟你们水平差不多的一抓一大把
But if you say you want real quality,
但如果你们想提高表演质量
first, you'll need stamina!
首先 你们需要耐力
Ten more uphill dashes!
再来十个上坡冲刺!
Eek!
哎呀!
And after you're exhausted, three run-throughs of the set list!
等你们筋疲力尽了 再排练三遍歌单
It's important to first have the stamina to keep your quality!
重要的是 首先要有保持质量的耐力
Don't forget to smile either!
也别忘了微笑!
Before the second song's chorus,
在第二首歌的副歌之前
if we come around from stage left and swapped out, wouldn't that be cool?!
如果我们从舞台左边转过来 交换一下 会很酷吧?
Oh, that sounds good!
听起来不错
Then what if we rearrange this too...
那我们也重新安排这个...
Where do they get all that energy from?
她们哪儿来的那么多精力?
Do you regret it?
你后悔吗?
Becoming an idol.
成为偶像
Mr. Pieyon...
啾啾仔先生
No, this is something I decided myself, so I have no regrets.
不后悔 这是我自己决定的 所以我不后悔
But I do think that I'm not cut out for this.
但我真的认为我不适合当偶像
I don't feel like I can become an idol at all.
我觉得我根本当不了偶像
Let alone the center.
更别说当C位了
You can sing, so why do you hate being the center so much?
你会唱歌 那你为什么那么讨厌当C位呢?
Well, because the center is the group's face, right?
因为C位是团体的门面吧?
It's not a position that someone like me should be in.
那不是我这样的人的位置
What do you mean "someone like me"?
“我这样的人”是什么意思?
I think Kana Arima is amazing.
我觉得有马加奈很了不起
Everyone always says things like that so easily.
大家总会轻易说出那样的话
Even when they don't know anything.
即使他们什么都不知道
What do you know about me?
你对我了解多少?
Let's see...
我想想
You're a hard worker who runs and does vocal exercises every morning.
你是个勤奋的人 每天早上跑步、练习声乐
Your foul mouth is your insecurity.
你骂人是因为你没有安全感
You're happier when the title is acknowledged more than yourself.
你扮演的角色得到认可 比你自己得到认可更令你开心
You actually hate green peppers.
你其实讨厌青椒
What? You know me really well!
什么?你真的很了解我
I'm thrilled...
好高兴啊
Well, he's got me pretty good.
他太了解我了
Crap. I think I like Pieyon a little now.
糟了 我觉得 我现在有点喜欢啾啾仔了
Are you perhaps my fan?
也许你是我的粉丝?
That's right.
没错
What? No way!
什么?不可能
I didn't know I had any fans right now.
我都不知道我现在有粉丝
I've never officially stated that I hated green peppers,
我从来没有正式说过我讨厌青椒
so I'm surprised you noticed.
所以我很惊讶你注意到了
In fact, I hate them too.
其实我也不喜欢青椒
We're comrades!
我们一样耶
That thing is too overpowering.
那东西让人无法忍受
It makes the whole dish taste like green peppers.
它让整道菜都是青椒味
I know!
我知道
During my "Green Pepper Exercise," I had to force myself to eat them.
录制《青椒运动》期间 我不得不逼着自己吃
Now, I break out in hives just looking at them.
现在我一看到它们就浑身起疹子
Poor thing.
真可怜啊
Do you hate chrysanthemum too?
你也讨厌茼蒿吗?
Yeah, I can't! It's as bitter as green peppers.
是的 我受不了 它们跟青椒一样苦
Hey...
喂
It's fun just talking casually with him.
跟他随便聊聊就很有趣
This is quite rare.
这可不多见
I feel like I can really fall for this person.
我觉得我真的会爱上这个人
Maybe I should just forget Aqua and move on to him.
也许我应该忘掉阿夸 转而喜欢他
He makes 100 million a year, so honestly, I would date him.
他一年赚一亿 说实话 我会跟他约会
Pieyon's so nice to come here every day when he must be busy.
啾啾仔人真好 每天都过来 他肯定很忙的
Right? You know, he looks completely different from his videos!
是吧?他本人跟视频里完全不同
I thought he would be more built,
我还以为他会更健美
but the real thing is surprisingly slender.
但他其实出奇地纤细
His physique is just like Aqua's!
他的身材跟阿夸一样
If my brother spoke in that duck voice, I wouldn't be able to stop laughing!
要是我哥用那鸭子的声音说话 我会笑个不停的
It's looking super good!
看起来非常好
Yeah, it's really good now!
是的 现在真的很好
Good work.
做得好
Thank you so much, Mr. Pieyon!
非常感谢你 啾啾仔先生
Gosh, he's so nice!
天啊 他人真好
Unlike someone called Aqua.
不像那个阿夸
Arima, do you hate Aqua that much?
有马 你那么讨厌阿夸吗?
There isn't a single thing you can like about him!
他哪儿都招人烦
He's insensitive and lacks common sense!
麻木不仁 缺乏常识
He acts cool, but he's just withdrawn.
装酷 其实是孤僻
Him and his sister both don't know how to treat their elders!
他跟他妹妹都不尊敬前辈
They've never used honorifics toward me either!
跟我说话从来不用敬语
I probably have to tell him off once!
我可能得说说他
I'm much older than Arima, but I don't remember her using honorifics.
我比有马大很多 但我不记得她用过敬语
Aww, he was cute when he was a kid.
他小时候可是很可爱的
Oh, you two go way back?
你们俩老早就认识?
That's right, we met on set when we were little!
没错 我们小时候在片场认识的
When Aqua and I were still three or four!
我和阿夸三四岁的时候
You know, you can't forget a guy like that once you meet him!
要知道 你见到那样的男孩就很难忘记
Ever since, he's always been in the back of my mind!
从那以后 他就一直在我的脑海里
I thought he was like an angel back then, but look how evil he's grown up to be!
我当时认为他和天使一样 但看他长大后多邪恶
I wish he wouldn't ruin my memories!
希望他不会毁了我的回忆!
Umm?
嗯?
Break's over! Let's practice!
休息结束了 我们练习吧
Tomorrow's finally the day.
明天是最后一天
How do you think they're doing?
你觉得她们怎么样?
I think they've gotten much better.
我觉得她们已经好多了
Ruby's dancing was already polished from the start.
露比的舞蹈一开始就打磨好了
Mem-cho can carefully move about as she watches her surroundings.
MEM啾可以小心翼翼地走动 同时观察周围的环境
And Ms. Arima is earnest and she learns quick.
有马很认真 学得很快
Even while she's singing, there aren't any obvious mistakes in her dancing.
即使在她唱歌的时候 她的舞蹈也没有任何明显的错误
MR. PIEYON
(啾啾仔先生)
This afternoon, have them practice with markers in mind, then rest for tomorrow.
今天下午让她们边熟悉场地标记 边练习 明天休息
Okay.
好的
Thank you for accepting a painstaking request like this during your vacation.
感谢你在度假期间 接受这样的艰苦请求
Well, I like those girls too.
我也喜欢那些女孩
So I'm glad you asked me for help.
所以很高兴你向我寻求帮助
But I'm a little shocked.
但我有点震惊
Since no one's noticed that you're impersonating me.
因为没有人注意到你在冒充我
It's impressive.
令人印象深刻
Can anyone who acts do this that easily?
演员能轻易做到这一点吗?
I don't know. I'm sure people who are good at it can do it.
我不知道 演技好的能做到吧
Hm.
是吗
But was this necessary?
但这有必要吗?
You didn't have to bother impersonating me...
你不必费心冒充我
She probably would've refused to listen to anything I said.
她可能会拒绝听我说的任何话
That's why I thought she would listen to your words, Mr. Pieyon.
啾啾仔先生的话 她或许会听
But I think she would've listened even if they were your words.
但我想 你的话 她也会听的
I'm... actually a pretty weak person.
我其实是个很软弱的人
It's finally here! We're gonna make our debut as idols!
终于来了 我们将以偶像的身份出道
What do we do?!
我们该怎么办?
Shut up.
好吵
Just go to sleep.
快睡觉吧
Don't underestimate the importance of sleep.
不要低估睡眠的重要性
"Some university's research says the damage from an all-nighter
“有大学研究表明 熬夜造成的伤害
will drag on for three days and decrease your charm by 30%."
会持续三天 使你的魅力下降三成”
That's what D**Go said.
这是**老师说的
D**Go did?! I gotta sleep then!
**老师说的?那我得睡觉了
But I'm not sleepy at all!
但我一点也不困
I'm too excited! What should I do?!
我太兴奋了 我该怎么办?
Seriously, it must be nice to be able to have so much fun.
说真的 能有这么多乐趣一定很不错
It must be horrible when you seem like you never have any fun.
前辈你看起来总是不能享受到快乐 这感觉一定很糟糕
Rather, why are you always so excited?
相反 你为什么总是那么兴奋?
Nobody can predict what'll happen tomorrow.
没有人能预测明天会发生什么
A group using connections like us might get booed like crazy.
像我们这种靠关系的团体 可能会被喝倒彩
Or maybe there won't be enough customers and the venue could be empty.
或者可能没什么观众 没人来看
How can you stay so positive like that?
你怎么能这么乐观?
Hmm.
嗯...
Because it's my dream.
因为这是我的梦想
A long time ago, I was living a life where I had to stay indoors all the time.
很久以前 我根本不能出门
I had no hope for the future.
我对未来不抱希望
I thought I would quietly die like that
我以为我会就这样悄悄地死去
without knowing any excitement or fun.
不知道兴奋和快乐的滋味
But...
但是...
My life became so fun after I became an idol otaku.
成为偶像御宅族后 我的生活变得非常有趣
My heart was filled with love.
我的心里充满了爱
The life of a fan is nice.
当粉丝的生活是美好的
If you've never liked an idol, Senpai, you're missing out in life.
如果你从来没有喜欢过偶像 学姐 你就错过了生活
I don't mind missing out.
我不介意错过
And so, that's when I met this one person.
所以就在那时 我遇到了这个人
One person?
一个人?
Yeah, my first love.
是的 我的初恋
Oh, how bittersweet.
苦乐参半啊
That person told me.
那个人告诉我
That he'll become my fan if I ever became an idol.
如果我成为偶像 他会成为我的粉丝
From that moment, I always dreamt of becoming an idol.
从那一刻起 我一直梦想着成为偶像
I wonder where Doctor is right now.
不知道医生现在在哪里
I'm sure he's still an idol otaku.
我相信他还是偶像宅男
So if I can become popular as an idol...
所以如果有一天我能
someday...
成为偶像...
That's nice, you have a fan to support you.
很好 你有个支持你的粉丝
I don't have anyone like that.
我身边 一个那样的人都没有
Everyone sees the child star in me.
大家都看到我是童星
But there's no one who sees me for who I am now.
但没有人看到我现在是谁
But it was surprising to know that Ruby was a shut-in.
但让人惊讶的是 露比以前是个不能出门的人
Aqua and the CEO went through a lot of trouble too.
阿夸和总裁也经历了很多麻烦
Pieyon's mask!
啾啾仔的面具
He never takes it off, so I was getting curious
他从不摘下来 所以我很好奇
what kind of face is behind that mask!
面具后面是怎样一张脸
Now, here we are at...
我们现在在
Japan Idol Festival!
日本偶像节!
Umm.
那个...
Of the 10 stages, the one we'll be performing on is the Star Stage.
在十个舞台中 我们要登上的是明星舞台
This stage has a lot of underground idols.
这个舞台有很多地下偶像
I would've preferred the main stage.
我更喜欢主舞台
But you know that's asking for too much.
但你知道这要求太过了
Ugh, I'm getting nervous now! I wonder if I'll be able to do okay.
我现在很紧张 我不知道我能不能做好
Don't worry! You got enough sleep, right?!
不用担心 你睡够了吧?
"'Some university's research says the damage from an all-nighter
“有大学研究表明 熬夜造成的伤害
will drag on for three days and decrease your charm by 30%.'
会持续三天 使你的魅力下降三成”
That's what Dai** said!" is what Senpai said!
这是**老师说的 学姐这么告诉我的
You're quoting someone who's quoting someone who's quoting someone.
你在引用别人引用的别人的话
Well, most of B Komachi's choreography is hard,
B小町大部分的编舞都很难
so it'll be tough if we don't sleep properly.
如果我们没睡好 就很难完成
Our main feature is the dancing, so we really gotta sleep well!
我们的主要特点是跳舞 所以我们真的要睡个好觉
What should I do? In the end, I couldn't sleep a wink.
我该怎么办? 最终 我一点也没睡着
Now, off to the dressing room.
现在去更衣室吧
Yay!
太好了!
- I wonder what the dressing room is like. - Aqua's under Pieyon's mask?
-我很好奇更衣室长什么样 -阿夸戴着啾啾仔的面具?
But he's not that buff.
但他不是啾啾仔啊
They swapped out? Why?
他们交换了?为什么?
Is it so I would take the lessons seriously?
这样我就会认真听课?
Was him being nice to me all a lie?
他对我那么温柔 都是谎言吗?
My head's a mess. When this is such an important day...
我脑子里很乱 在这个非常重要的日子...
Jeez, this is the worst.
天啊 这是最糟的
Let's hurry to the dressing room. Then I can sleep a little.
我们赶紧去更衣室吧 然后我可以睡一会儿
It's not that way!
不是那边
What?
什么?
The stage dressing room can only be used right before your turn.
快轮到你们的时候 你们才能用舞台更衣室
Really?
是这样的吗?
Then where do we change?
那我们在哪儿换衣服?
Hey, move your stuff over!
把你们的东西搬过来
Ugh, does anyone have a pantyliner?!
有人有护垫吗?
What is this hellhole?
这是什么样的地狱场面?
The dressing room.
更衣室啊
The number of people here is insane.
这里的人也太多了
This is pretty normal for festivals with many stages.
对于舞台这么多的偶像节来说 这很正常
Hundreds of performers and staff are all squeezed in together
数百名艺人和工作人员挤在一起
with no place for your luggage.
行李没地方放
There isn't even a real dressing room, so you change behind the room dividers.
甚至没有真正的更衣室 所以你们在房间隔板后面换衣服
But the photo spot alone looks really nice.
但拍照区看起来真不错
This is chaos.
这简直是一团糟
Of course, the famous groups invited to the main stage get separate rooms.
当然 受邀到主舞台演出的著名团体 有单独的房间
But underground or so-so idols are all treated like this.
但地下偶像 和普通偶像的待遇就是这样
If you want to be treated better, you have to become popular.
如果你们想得到更好的待遇 那就必须受观众欢迎
Now, it'll get busy before your turn, so eat or get prepared while you can.
好了 在到你们之前我还有事要忙 所以趁有时间 吃点东西 做好准备
Okay!
好的
All this heated excitement...
所有这些热烈的兴奋...
Are you okay?
你没事吧?
Well, I'm just a little sleep-deprived.
我只是有点睡眠不足
Oh, are you nervous?
你紧张吗?
Please, don't be silly.
拜托 别傻了
I've been in this industry since I was sucking on a bottle.
我从捧着奶瓶开始就进了演艺圈
There's no way I would get nervous now.
我现在不可能紧张
Just leave the two to me.
就把这两个交给我吧
Really.
是吗...
Can I have a minute?
过来一下 好吗?
Oh, yes.
好的
That's right, I have to take care of this group.
没错 我必须照顾好这个团体
With my 17 years of showbiz experience, I have to lead those two hatchlings.
我得用我出道17年的经验 来带领这两个小孩
Don't be overwhelmed by the atmosphere.
不要被氛围冲昏头脑
Don't be scared. Get it together!
不要害怕 振作起来
There's a ton of people's jobs on my shoulders.
我肩负着很多人的工作
If I screw up, everyone's screwed.
如果我搞砸了 所有人都得完蛋
And I would betray the trust and expectations they have of me.
我会背叛他们对我的信任和期望
I just remembered something bad.
我想起了一些不好的事情
I can't think negatively.
我不能往坏了想
The look of disappointment that says, "I guess this is it."
那个失望的表情在说 “我就知道是这样”
The staff joins the crowd in their own clothes
工作人员穿着自己的衣服加入人群
just so the seats look more filled.
就为了让座位看起来更满
Well, let's stop here once, and we'll release the next one when the time comes.
让我们在这里停一下 我们将在时机成熟时发布下一个
Um, is there any work I can do?
有什么工作我可以做吗?
I'll do any--
我会做任何...
Uh, well, we're a child acting agency,
我们是一家儿童表演机构
so work at your age is a little tough.
适合你这个年纪的工作有点难
I'm sure there's jobs for you at a normal agency though.
不过我相信 一般的机构里肯定有你能做的工作
Grandpa injured his back,
爷爷伤了背
so Mama's thinking of going back home.
所以妈妈想回家去
Kana, you'll be fine by yourself, right?
加奈 你一个人可以的吧?
Of course I'll be fine!
我当然可以
Mama, you get rested up too!
妈妈 你也休息一下
Am I not needed anymore?
他们不再需要我了吗?
KANA ARIMA STARS IN I'LL GO WITH SWEET TODAY
(有马加奈出演 《今天就稍微甜一点》)
IS THERE ANY VALUE TO HER NOW?
(她现在还有价值吗?)
THE GROWN-UP ARIMA HAS NO FANS.
(成年后的有马没有粉丝)
There's no value in me who isn't a child actress anymore!
不再是童星的我就没有价值了
The grown-up Kana Arima has no fans!
成年的有马加奈没有粉丝
Since when...
什么时候开始...
When did I start self-deprecating with words that sound like internet comments?
我什么时候开始用这些类似 网络评论的词语 来妄自菲薄了?
Lead the B Komachi?
领导B小町?
How arrogant of me to even consider it.
我可真傲慢 还敢这么想
But I have to do it.
但我必须这样做
I have to take care of those two.
我必须照顾好这两个人
Umm.
嗯...
Oh, Senpai!
学姐
Oh my gosh!
不好了
I'm getting super nervous!
我变得超级紧张
What?!
什么?
You seemed like you were enjoying yourself just a second ago.
你刚才好像还很享受
As our turn got closer, I gradually...
离我们上场的时间越近 我渐渐...
What should I do?
我该怎么办?
Senpai, aren't you scared?
学姐 你不害怕吗?
Of course not.
当然不怕
How many years do you think I've been doing this?
你以为我出道多少年了?
Everyone always lies like that.
大家总这么撒谎
Your hands are super cold.
你的手超级凉
Senpai, you're nervous too, aren't you?
学姐 你也很紧张吧?
Don't be stupid!
别傻了!
I never sank so low as to where I need you to worry about me!
我从来没有堕落到 需要你为我担心的地步
The small insecure dogs tend to bark more.
没有安全感的小狗更容易吠叫
But I'm glad.
但我很高兴
I feel relieved to know that you're scared too.
知道你也害怕我就放心了
Huh? Are you pretty seriously scared?
什么?你真的很害怕吗?
You'll be fine!
你会没事的
We're not doing this alone!
我们还有彼此
That's why!
就是这个原因!
That's why it isn't good!
这样才不好
It's because of you guys!
因为你们
If I was going up on stage alone, I would think nothing of it.
如果我一个人上台 我什么都不会想
I've failed like that repeatedly up to this point.
到目前为止 我已经失败很多次了
But this time, you two are here.
但这一次 你们两个在这儿
I don't want you to fail.
我不希望你们失败
I don't want you two to go through what I experienced.
我不希望你们两个 经历我所经历过的事情
I'm not alone, that's why I'm scared.
我不是一个人 所以我很害怕
I don't know much about your child actress days.
我对你的童星时代了解不多
And I don't know how much you value your showbiz experience,
我不知道你有多看重你的演艺圈经历
but to me, you're just a young girl.
但对我来说 你只是个年轻的女孩
You're just a cute and hardworking rookie idol found anywhere.
你只是一个可爱又勤奋的新秀偶像
Screwing up is normal!
搞砸了很正常
Let's enjoy the challenge!
让我们享受挑战吧!
Come on, it's our turn to change! Let's go, Senpai!
来吧 到我们换衣服了 我们走吧 学姐
Oh my gosh!
我的天啊
I'm super nervous!
我超级紧张
But I'm so excited!
但是我很兴奋
I am a rookie.
我是个新秀
The rookie idol, Kana Arima.
新秀偶像 有马加奈
Subtitle translation by: Kanami Kitabayashi
字幕翻译:宋宛娇